Maxime Faget Papers
University of Houston-Clear Lake Archives & Special Collections
- Series XVI: Publications and Technical Reports
  - A Three Stage Launch Vehicle Using Flyback Delta, Castor IV-B, or Bus 7" Demonstration Orbit, August 31, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Report to NASA Federal Laboratory Review Task Force, November 28-29, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Strategic Thinking for Space: An Unfolding Story by Kenneth J. Cox, September 1995 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Photocopy of Article by James Oberg Shuttle-Mir Lessons for the International Space Station, IEEE Spectrum, June 1998 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - There are More Things Horatio, by William E. Stoney, February 11, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Draft: Technologies of Manned Space Systems Chapters 1, 2, and 3, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Draft: Technologies of Manned Space Systems Chapters 4, 6, 7, and 8, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Memoir: For Wallops Island to Mercury by: Robert R. Gilruth, 1945-1958 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence Related to Final Draft of Space Exploration Encyclopedia Entry, August 1978 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Long Range Outlook for US Government Expenditures on Space, December 1982 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - An Historical Overview of NASA Manned Spacecraft and Their Crew Stations by Joseph P. Loftus, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - LSU /Alumni News 1971 with Letter of Gift, April 13, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Statement by Faget to Subcommittee on Space Science and Applications, Committee on Science, Space and Technology US House of Representatives 100th Congress, March 23, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Letter from Encyclopedia of Space Science and Technology, March 8, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Technologies of Manned Space Systems by Aleck C. Bond and Faget, Draft, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Pre-Operational Aerodynamic Design Data Book Volume 1 Obiter Vehicle, April 1982 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Pre-Operational Aerodynamic Design Data Book Volume 1 Obiter Vehicle, April 1982 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Series XVII: Space Industries
  - Space Industries A Bold Plan to Make Commercial Space Industrialization a Reality, circa 1980s (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Photograph of Max Faget: Space Industries Era, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Space Station The Next Logical Step, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Space Industries Presentation, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Houston Career Digest, November 1981 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clipping: Triumph in Space: A Man to Remember, November 17, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Arthur Young Letter - Space Industries A Proposal to Provide Professional Services, 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Space Industries Business Papers, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Eagle Engineering Contract, January 7, 198? (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - University of Houston Space Statin Applications, January 12, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Space Industries Meeting with Ronald Reagan, Newspaper Clipping, August 1983 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Space Industries Booklets, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Shuttle Flight Price, August 12, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Space Industries Agreement with NASA Space Systems Development and Office of Space Station, August 20, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Texas Business Cover and Article, March 1986 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Water-Propellant Resistojets for Man-Tended Platforms, Space Industries, October 10-17, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Space Industries: Air Force Meeting, October 20-21, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Space Industries: The Business of Space, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Space Industries Articles and Memos, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Space Industries International, INC. Offering and Sale of $6,000,000 of Common Stock, September 1, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Space Industries Master Mailing List, March 10, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings Space Industries, January 12-May 20, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Space Industries Moves, February 28-June 17, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Space Industries: Nomination of C. C. Johnson for Gilruth Award by Faget, July 24, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Space Industries: A Low Cost Commercial Approach to Space Systems Development and Operations, August 28-September 5, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Space Industries/Arvin Industries Merger Press Release, September 1, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Space Industries Arvin Merger Newspaper Clippings, September 2, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Space Industries Employee Roster, August 26, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Cooperative Activities - NPO Energomash and Pratt and Whitney Joint Marketing and Technology Licensing Agreement, undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Space Industries Employee Roster, September 21, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Space Industries in the News, October November 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Photographs -Space Industries Faget Publicity Photos, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Space Industries in the News, January 1988 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Space Industries Stock Questionnaire, April 20, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Policy Issues Pertaining to the Space Exploration Initiative, August 8-10, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Space Industries Memorandum, December 20, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Risk Etc. O. G. Risk Management, 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Space Station Orbiter, July 9, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - SII Study Report for Rockwell Expanded Orbiter Missions, September 1991 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Space Industries Orbiter Derived Space Station Freedom Concept, September 1991 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Black and White Photograph Max Faget Space Industries, February 27, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Space Industries: Leading the Commercial Development of Space Professional Experience Employee Summaries, undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Series XVIII: Industrial Space Facility
  - Color Photographs Artist Rendering of Industrial Space Facility, 1980s (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of Industrial Space Station Model, 1980s (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Satellite Photographs and Photograph of Industrial Space Facility Model, circa 1980s (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Industrial Space Facility Brochure, 1980s (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - R&D Study for an Industrial Space Facility, June 1984 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Industrial Space Facility Baseline Design, October 1984 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Agreement Between NASA and Space Industries for a Joint Endeavor Concerning Research and Development of an Industrial Space Facility for Commercial Operations, Proposed First Draft, November 8, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Space Industries: Industrial Space Facility Presentation Book, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Industrial Space Facility Presentation, 1980s (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Industrial Space Facility Structural Report ISF-Prephase II Program, March 5, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Industrial Space Facility Structural Report ISF-Prephase II Program, Part 11, March 5, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Color Photographs of Industrial Space Facility Model by C. C. Johnson, 1980s (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Industrial Space Facility Proprietary Space Industries Program Approach, 1980s (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Industrial Space Facility Schematics, 1980s (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Industrial Space Facility Configurations Brochure, 1980s (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Industrial Space Facility Clippings, 1980s-1990s (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Blueprints of Space Station with Letter of Explanation, February-March-1993 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Industrial Space Facility Concept and Structures System, August 1983 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Industrial Space Facility Presentations, August 16, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Industrial Space Facility Presentations, September 1983 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Colored Drawing of Industrial Space Facility and Copies of Phase I Drawings, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - R&D Study for an Industrial Space Facility, June 1984 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Space Industries: Industrial Space Station Designs and Memos, 1984; 1985 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Industrial Space Facility Schematics and Memos, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Space Hab Venture Industrial Space Facility, 1980s (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Industrial Space Facility Final Drafts of Various Documents, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Space Industries Space Facility Baseline Design, October 1985 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Industrial Space Facility Program Brochure, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Industrial Space Facility: An Overview, August 1985 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Space Industries is Making Plans with NASA for a Space Facility, Fall 1985 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Industrial Space Facility Primary and Secondary Design Specification, March 5, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Industrial Space Facility and the U. S. Space Station, July 21, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Industrial Space Facility Baseline Design, February 1987 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Industrial Space Facility Press Release, Brochure and Photo, September 21, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Preliminary Report Space Facility Test and Verification Plan, October 15, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Cancellation of Commercially Developed Space Facility, April 1989 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Schematics of Space Station, undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Oversized Box Blueprints of Industrial Space Station, 1980s (Box 55)
- Series XIX: Photographs
  - School Photograph of Boy and Girl, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Photo Negatives of Tornado, House, Party, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Photograph of Satellite, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Pictures of Faget on Carousel, undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Photographs from Beth to Judy of Faget at SIII, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Photograph Christmas, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - NASA Photograph of Faget 1959 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Lunar Exploration Mission Profile Photographs, 1960s (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Photograph of Faget 1960 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Color Prints of Sigma 7, October 3, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Official NASA Photograph of Faget 1962 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Official NASA Photograph of Faget 1964 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Photograph - Visit by Achievement Rewards for College Scientist Foundation to the Manned Spacecraft Center, April 27, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Copy of First Photo of Earth Taken from Lunar Distance, August 23, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Various NASA Photographs, 1967-1981 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Photographs of Faget at Johnson Space Center, 1969-1979 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Black and White Photographs of S-IC Stage and F1 Engine, undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Headshot of Faget, undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Black and White Image of Rocket with Two Men, undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Production Scene List Locator Dynamic and Visual Simulation of Selected Earth Orbital Operations Production Number CL-72-591, undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
    Found with Film CL 72-602
  - Production Scene List Locator Dr. Faget's Film Presentation Production Number CL 70-526, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
    See Film Series for Film CL 70-526
  - E&D Staff Assistants Photographs, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Mounted Color Original Art Son of Mark I, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Photograph of JSC Director Gerald D. Griffin and Charlie Walker, 1980s (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Photograph of Faget with Family, undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Pictures of Space Flights, circa 1960s (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Photographs of 1961 Visit to General Electric (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Photographs taken by Ranier VII, July 31, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Photographs of Manned Spacecraft Center, March 30, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Summary Film for Skylab Experiments M509 Astronauts Maneuvering Equipment CL 727, May 1966 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    Found with Film CL 727
  - Airplane or Shuttle Model in Flight with Faget, Black and White, undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Letter and Photograph Visit to McDonnell Douglas, April 30, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Photographs: NASA Photograph of Faget in 1964 and 1981 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Color Photographs of Faget in Meeting, 1970s (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Photographs of Jupiter and its Satellites Taken by Voyager 1, May 4, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Photographs from Dryden Flight Research Center Photo Gallery, undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Photograph of Faget, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Photographs 1968 of Manned Spacecraft Center (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Official NASA Photograph of Faget, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - NASA Photograph of Donald K. Slayton, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Photograph of Faget in USSR Envelope with Russian Stamps, June 18, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Photographs of MISTEL 2, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Various NASA Photographs, 1959-1970s (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Photographs of Faget and Chet Huntley with Letter, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Black and White NASA Photographs, 1966-1968 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Black and White NASA Photographs, 1966-1970s (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Photographs of Faget and other NASA Employees, June 1965 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Official NASA Photographs of Faget, 1960s-1970s (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Length of Service Award Photographs, 1970-1974 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Faget's Photographs, Late 1070s to 1984 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Space Operations Center Documents and Photos, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Satellite Photograph of Earth, undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - The 1981 Maxmoble (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Photographs of Faget in Meeting, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Photograph of Swigert Memorial Ball, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Photographs Faget and Robert Crippen, 1980-1982 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - undated Photographs, circa 1990s (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Photographs of Reunion 50th LSU, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Photographs of Faget on Trip to Tokyo, Japan Asakusa District, undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Photocopy of Max Faget's Passport Issued September 10, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Email Printout from Nanette Cerna to Michael Plaxton, May-June 2002 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Max Faget and Hugh Downs Photograph, undated (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Official Photograph of Faget Various Sizes, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Various Design NASA Photographs, 1958-1980s (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - 25th Anniversary NASA Photograph of Shuttle, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Photograph from Pat Templeton, January 8, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Photographs from Melanie Wiggins to Max Faget on Belize, March 29, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Loose Photographs, circa 1991 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Photographs from Donald Rathburn, December 17, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Photograph of USS Prairie State Space Industries Capsule, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Max and Aleck Photograph, January 11, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Photograph with Note of Transhab Technical Independent Assessment, November 6-7, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Photograph of Young Faget with Christmas Card from Doris Drake, December 20, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Photographs from Cruise, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Pictures of Cruise, Dog, Family, circa 2001 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Pictures of Trip to France, May 20, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Photographs of Angel Island, September 2002 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Pacific Coast Trip Photographs with Notes, September 17-25, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Gallery of NASA Employee Photographs, Circa 1960s (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Facebook of NASA Employees Staff OFC Manned Spacecraft Center, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Facebook of NASA Employees Crew Sys Manned Spacecraft Center, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Facebook of NASA Employees C&AD Manned Spacecraft Center, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Facebook of NASA Employees IESD Manned Spacecraft Center, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Facebook of NASA Employees G&CD Manned Spacecraft Center, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Facebook of NASA Employees P&PD Manned Spacecraft Center, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Facebook of NASA Employees SMD Manned Spacecraft Center, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Facebook of NASA Employees ASTD Manned Spacecraft Center, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Series XX: Slides
  - American Samoa/New Zealand Slides, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Antarctic Slides, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Germany, Lake Constance Harbor at Lindau, England Slides, October 1970 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Slides and Processing Bag Russia 1973 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Russia Visit Slides, September 1974 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Samoa, New Zealand, McMurdo Base, Scott's Hut Slides, undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Ceramic Engineering Slides of Electron Microscope, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - NASA Retirement Slides, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Slides and Film Negatives of Event outside Teague Auditorium, Johnson Space Center, December 1981 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Hotel Pago Pago and School Children Slides, January 1967 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Slides of Foreign Travel, August 1974-March 1975 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Slides of Spacelab Program, undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Artist Representation of Faget Shuttle Concept Slides, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Lake and Home Interior Slide, undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Various Slides of Mercury, Apollo, and Shuttle, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Various Shuttle Concepts, 1975-1981 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Slides of Shuttle and Apollo, 1977-1980 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Various Slides, undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Series XXI: Newspaper Clippings
  - Newspaper Clipping of Faget Commissioning and Engagement, 1940s (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Clipping Restored First Photo to Return, undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings Mercury, Late 1950s-1962 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Houston Science Fair Newspaper Clipping, March 17, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - NASA Roundups and other Clippings, 1960s-1979 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - NASA Roundup with Org Chart, November 25, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - NASA Roundup, 1966-1967 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - NASA Current News, April 11, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1961-1967 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - University of Pittsburgh Alumni Times, October 1971 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - The Daily Reveille LSU, November 12, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - NASA Roundup, May 5, 1971 and; June 22, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - High School for Engineering Professions Newsletter Volume 1, Number 3, November 3, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Houston Career Digest, November 2, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - NASA Roundup, September 30, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - USA Today Money Section, November 13, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1988-1990 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - NASA Roundup, July 14, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Mignon Faget Clippings, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper Clippings Space Industries Galveston Daily News, January 31, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - The Houston Post, August 26, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - The New Yorker Annals of Space, September 2, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Sunday Advocate Once a Dumping Ground, Hansen's Disease Center is No Longer End of World, November 20, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Photocopies of Omni Magazine Article: Max Faget Master Builder, April 1995 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Clipping Shuttle Pioneer Calls for End to Manned Flights, May 16, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Space Center Roundup, August 2004 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Space Center Roundup, November 2004 (Box 44, Folder 28)
- Series XXII: Other Media
  - Magnetic Tape of Max Faget New Report with Letter from KTRK Channel 13 TV Anchor Sylvan Rodriguez (Aired August 15, 1981; Letter Dated July 13, 1983) (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Various Floppy Discs, CDs, and Tapes, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Series XXIII Series 23 - Oversize (Legal Size) Items
  - Hansen's Disease Clippings, undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Large Mercury Planning Book with undated Clippings, 1950s (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - The Star: Radiating the Light of Truth on Hansen's Disease, January 1950 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - US Navy Correspondence Course Lessons and Diagrams, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - The Star: Radiating the Light of Truth on Hansen's Disease, September-October 1958 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - The Star: Radiating the Light of Truth on Hansen's Disease, May-June 1959 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - The Star: Radiating the Light of Truth on Hansen's Disease, January-February 1961 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - The Star: Radiating the Light of Truth on Hansen's Disease, March-April 1962 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - The Star: Radiating the Light of Truth on Hansen's Disease, May-June 1971 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Space Station Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Various Newspaper Clippings, 1962-1963 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Louisiana State University Officials Night, January 22, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Invitation to Fort George Hotel Belize, December 22, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Patent Disclosure: Powered Pool and Billiard Shooter, December 23, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Apollo 11 Commemorative Manifest, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Series XXIV: Scrapbooks
  - Scrapbook (restricted), 1962 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Pages for 1963 Scrapbook (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook - Includes Antarctica Trip and Patent for Capsule, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook - Includes Apollo Information, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook - Elected as AIAA Fellow, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook - Hurricane Claudette, July-October 1979 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook, 1978-1981 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Series XXV: Periodicals
  - Aerospace Engineering Volume 18 Number 4, April 1960 (Box 49)
  - LSU Alumni News 2 Copies, October 1961 (Box 49)
  - Celle Qui Pleure Volume XXIII, Number 3, March 1962 (Box 49)
  - Time Magazine - No Cover, March 2, 1962 (Box 49)
  - Newsweek Volume LIX Number 23, June 4, 1962 (Box 49)
  - Newsweek Volume LX Number 15 - 2 Copies, October 8, 1962 (Box 49)
  - Astronautics and Aerospace Engineering: A Publication of the American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics, February 1963 (Box 49)
  - Civil Service Journal Volume 4 Number 2, October-December 1963 (Box 49)
  - Astronautics and Aerospace Engineering: A Publication of the American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics, February 1964 (Box 49)
  - Newsweek Volume LXIX Number 6, February 6, 1967 (Box 49)
  - Aviation Week and Space Technology Volume 91 Number 17, October 27, 1969 (Box 49)
  - LSU/Alumni News - 2 Copies, June 1971 (Box 49)
  - Texas Monthly Volume 14 Number 7, July 1986 (Box 49)
  - Spinoff, 1986 (Box 49)
  - Texas Business Volume X Number 9 - 3 Copies, March 1986 (Box 49)
  - Power Systems News, November-December 1986 (Box 49)
  - TransStar, April 1987 (Box 49)
  - The New Yorker, March 7, 1988 (Box 49)
  - Spirit Southwest Airlines - 3 Copies, April 1988 (Box 50)
  - Discover Volume 9 Number 7 - 2 Copies, July 1988 (Box 50)
  - Space World: Published in cooperation with the National Space Society, September 1988 (Box 50)
  - Air & Space Smithsonian Volume 3 Number 5, December 1988-January 1989 (Box 50)
  - Spirit of Apollo: A Collection of Reflective Interviews: American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics - Houston Section - 3 Copies, July 1989 (Box 50)
  - Lear's Volume 2 Number 7 - 2 Copies, October 1989 (Box 50)
  - The First Lunar Landing As Told by the Astronauts 20th Anniversary, 1989 (Box 50)
  - AIAA Student Journal: A Publication of the American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics Volume 29 Number 1, Spring 1991 (Box 50)
  - The New Yorker - 2 Copies, September 2, 1991 (Box 50)
  - Omni Volume 17 Number 7, April 1995 (Box 50)